Listen, Hananoi-kun.
When I was in elementary school,
this weird rumor went around that I had a
crush on a boy that my friend liked.
It wasn't true, of course, and I denied it.
But I didn't try very hard to explain things
to my friend, and it really hurt her.
Is this the friend who cut your hair?
Yup.
We were so close, too.
It made me realize that love
can change you, and that scared me.
But I've always felt like if I'd understood
what it meant to like someone,
maybe things would have
turned out differently.
The reason I wanted to date you
and learn what love means
was partly because of that.
Hey, Hananoi-kun, doesn't the idea that
you or I might change someday scare you?
For me, before I started dating you,
food was just sustenance in my eyes.
You taught me how delicious it can be.
If love has the power to change
people for the worse,
it must also have the power
to change us for the better.
That's what I realize when I watch you.
S-Say, Hananoi-kun...
Maybe you won't want this
since we baked our own.
But I really like you, Hananoi-kun.
I'm... in love with you!
Episode 7
My First Confession
Thank you.
I'm...
so happy.
Are you sure about this?
Are you sure what you're feeling is love?
Well, Kyo-chan says that love means
different things for different people.
So it might not be the
exact same thing you feel,
but I do think this is love!
You know, I really do like you.
I want to be with you all the time.
Uh-huh.
As long as I have you,
I don't care about anyone else.
I don't need family or friends.
Huh?
I always want to be close to you,
and I don't want to let anyone else near.
I want all of you all to myself.
Knowing that, do you still
think you can love me?
Gosh, it sure is cold!
Oh dear. Is somebody home?
Didn't you say you were going out today?
Grandma.
H-How do you do?!
My!
What's this?! Did you sneak a girl in
to be alone together?
I know your parents aren't around,
but that doesn't mean you can just go wild!
I certainly hope you weren't
doing anything naughty.
Huh?
Don't say it like that.
D-D-Definitely not!
Um, we were only baking
chocolate cake together!
Chocolate cake?
Well, I do smell something nice.
U-Um, I'll be on my way.
If you'd like, please try some.
Oh, wait. I'll walk you out.
I'm sorry. My grandma is pretty
strict about that kind of stuff.
No, it's okay.
Oh no! The train's coming!
Hurry up!
Hotaru-chan!
Wait for me!
Th-Thank you.
H-Here is fine. Thanks for walking with me.
Sure.
Hey, Hotaru-chan.
Maybe we shouldn't talk for a while.
Huh?
I want you to think seriously
about what I said today.
Once you've made up your mind,
we can pick up where we left off.
B-But I really do...
It's okay. I know.
Oh man...
There you go again,
trying to act like a good kid.
When you really want something,
why don't you just say so?
Sometimes you should just be honest,
sonny.
I'm such an idiot.
Think seriously about it, huh?
As long as I have you,
I don't care about anyone else.
I want all of you all to myself.
All of me?
Hananoi
Let's stop walking to school
and eating lunch together
for a while
Call received
The Next Day
Hotako.
Oh!
What's up? You keep looking around.
Oh, um, it's nothing.
He really didn't come.
He's stopped messaging me every day, too.
Hananoi!
Oh?
I'll never ask you for anything else!
Help me study!
Why me?
Hell no.
But you're super smart, right?
If I don't do better this school year,
they'll drop me from the starting lineup!
Come on, Hananoi! I'm begging you!
Wait. Isn't today the day you
always eat with Hananoi-san?
Yeah...
Oh!
Can you pick something up for me?
Can you grab something at the
4-chome supermarket?
Ugh.
Um, she also wanted... salad dressing?
There it is!
Oh!
I'm sorry!
Huh?
Oh my, it's you! The girl from before.
You're Hananoi-kun's...
My name is Hinase Hotaru!
I apologize for the other day!
Not at all. I should apologize to you.
I shouldn't have snapped at you
like that. I'm sorry, dear.
Oh.
I didn't realize it at the time,
but you're who called
me last year, aren't you?
You left before I could thank you
properly. It's been bothering me.
So once again, you have my gratitude.
I-It was nothing.
Say, do you live near here too, Hinase-san?
Huh? Yes.
In that case, might I have
a bit more of your time?
It's getting cold, dear.
Oh, right!
Oh, I see.
You've baked together and visited
a shrine with friends...
I suppose this means that boy is
enjoying a normal high school life.
That's quite a relief.
You know, he never tells me anything at all.
I-Is that right?
If it turned out he was living
an unhealthy lifestyle,
I was thinking of dragging
him back to live with me.
Why does Hananoi-kun live alone now?
Oh, didn't he tell you? About his parents?
He said they're doctors who work overseas.
Well, it's not exactly work.
They're practically volunteers.
You see, his parents travel back
and forth to poor countries,
helping children who can't
afford medical treatment.
I saw a show about people like that on TV!
Well, what they're doing is wonderful,
except they go around helping other peoples'
children while ignoring their own son.
I took care of him
while he was living with me.
I wonder if he was embarrassed by that.
Once he started high school, he wanted
to move back into the old apartment alone.
He's a good boy, but he can be
a bit extreme sometimes.
Yeah.
Though he's changed a little recently.
He never seemed to care
much for food before,
but now he asks me about cooking
and even cleans his plate.
I wonder who
is having an effect on him.
Huh?
By the way, what happened to your hand?
Oh, this little thing?
When I went over to cook for him,
I goofed and burned myself.
I told him it'd heal on its own,
but he dragged me to the hospital.
It isn't such a big deal. Don't worry, okay?
Hananoi
Let's stop walking to school
and eating lunch together for a while
I'm good just holding one person truly dear.
Hananoi
I've been thinking about a lot
Let's stop walking to school
and eating lunch together
for a while
Call received
I've been thinking about a lot
since we've been apart.
I'm starting to understand that "special"
things are deeply important to you.
But when you say you
don't care about anyone else,
I don't think you really feel that way.
I'm sure you have your reasons
for saying it, though.
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
are deeply important to you. But when
you say you don't care about anyone else,
I don't think you really feel that way.
I'm sure you have your reasons for
saying it, though.
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
are deeply important to you. But when
you say you don't care about anyone else,
I don't think you really feel that way.
I'm sure you have
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
are deeply important to you. But when
you say you don't care about anyone else,
I don't think you really feel that way.
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
are deeply important to you. But when
you say you don't care about anyone else,
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
are deeply important to you. But when
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
are deeply important to you.
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
I've been thinking about a lot since
we've been apart. I'm starting
to understand that "special" things
When I can't see him,
I get so lonely.
I miss you, Hananoi-kun
H-Hananoi-kun?
Ah! Hotaru-chan?
Sorry to surprise you.
I got your message.
O-Oh, yeah.
So, actually, right now...
Sorry. I'm here.
Hotaru?
Where are you going at this hour?
Just the convenience store!
Hananoi-kun!
Oh! S-Sorry!
I've been so Hotaru deprived,
I wasn't thinking!
Me too! I've missed you so much!
So...
I'm positive I like you, Hananoi-kun.
But when you ask if I'm sure about it,
I'm not sure I can keep up with
you on all your sense of values.
I'm not confident I'll be an ideal girlfriend.
I mean, I don't have any reason
whatsoever to be confident.
But you know...
Can't we still be together,
even if we see things differently?
The other day when we were baking
together, I was so happy.
But it wasn't just then.
There have been so many occasions
that were a delight.
Where I was thrilled to be with you,
or even just to talk to you.
I figure maybe, as those things keep
adding up, I'll find my confidence.
So, you know, I think this
is just the beginning.
I want it to be you, Hananoi-kun.
Things may not always work,
and I might cry sometimes,
but you're who I want to share that with.
So do you think you could go out
with someone like me?
That's what... I should be asking you.
What? Why are you crying?
I'm not crying.
Oh, really? Sorry, my mistake.
I'm sorry. I'm the one lacking confidence.
He really is crying.
I love you.
Y-You flatter me.
I'm looking forward to us.
So... So am I!
D-Does this mean we're about to—
It's winter. I'm sixteen.
And starting today, we really
are boyfriend and girlfriend.
The Horse and the Witch
Hey there.
All by yourself again, sonny?
What's going on? You look
even gloomier than normal.
My mom and dad promised to
come back to Japan next week,
but now they can't.
Is that right?
Well, a doctor's life is
always full of surprises.
The Horse and the Witch
I wonder if even they care about me at all.
Well, I guess it's about time for you.
Your parents are living as they please,
so you should live freely too.
You gotta find someone else
that you really love.
More than Mom and Dad?
Yeah! That's what they call...
a soulmate!
In my case, I lived a little too freely,
so my folks cut ties with me.
But when I met my wife,
it changed my universe.
A soulmate?
So, how about it?
Any girls you like at school?
No.
Get out there, sonny!
You've got your whole life ahead of you.
Early day tomorrow,
so I'm headed to sleep!
Night!
Night
Morning, Hotaru-chan
Hotaru-chan
Good morning
Early day tomorrow,
so I'm headed to sleep!
Night!
Night
Morning, Hotaru-chan
Hinase Hotaru
Good morning, Hananoi-kun!
I got so excited yesterday, I couldn't sleep at all
Same
Hinase Hotaru
I turn so red when I remember we're in love
Starting today, I'm your girlfriend!
Hananoi-kun, I'm... in love with you!
What am I gonna do?
I'm so happy.
Flour Bakery
-Soft and chewy on the inside
-Crust is also good
Hotaru-chan would love it
I miss you, Hotaru-chan